

# **Hunter Warren**

hunterwarren.codes

hunter.warren@gmail.com

512.557.5032

#### **About Me**

I'm a Front-End Developer who's transitioned to programming after 7+ years experience as an Advertising Art Director /Designer. What excites me about developing software is the potential to improve and enrich people's lives through the use of technology.

#### **SKILLS:**

#### **Programming Software** Professional/Interpersonal JS / CSS / SCSS / HTML Photoshop, Illustrator, Visual design and mass React / Redux / ES6 inDesign, After Effects, communication sensibilites Java, PHP Premiere, Audition Presentation experience MySQL, Git • Excel, Google Sheets • Familiar with creative feedback Node, NPM, Bash • Powerpoint, Keynote process, and team collaboration OldLister (codeup)

#### **PROJECTS:**

## Asana API (usaa)

Using Asana's API, I created a form for CDO Storefront Project Managers to create Asana tasks and submit them to various project backlogs. Built with React, USAA components, Axios API calls.

# Using vanilla PHP, MySQL,

HTML and custom CSS, we built a Craigslist clone allowing people to buy and sell goods, while allowing anyone to browse what's for sale.

# Globetrotter.pro (codeup)

A mobile-responsive app for travel budgeting. Built with Laravel, we use PHP to call an API with cost data from 30,00 locations. User budgets are built with a jQuery and JavaScript 'wizard' and stored in a MySQL database, which is managed with Laravel.

#### **WORK:**

### **Previous Experience**

#### 2017-current

# Front-End Developer at USAA

Work within the Chief Design Office on a team of Front-End Developers of wide-ranging expertise to build pages for USAA's digital storefront. Most pages involve a significant degree of custom HTML, CSS & JS, as our team's storefront pages can't use frameworks or rely on external libraries. QA designs with their respective designers and project stakeholders, and with Accessibility Ops team. Upload all page code into Tridion CMS, and maintain CSS for other teams within Tridion. Contribute to a library of components used by our storefront FED's to faciliate rapid development of pages. Over the past 6 months, have been using Node, NPM, SCSS, and scripting to more quickly develop pages.

#### 2012-2017

# **Art Director / Interactive Designer at DDB New York**

Digital, Social, Video and 360 advertising campaign work for Clean & Clear, State Farm, Frigidaire, Electrolux, Lipton, Breyers, Exxon Mobil, and Royal Canin. Also responsible for digital content creation / content optimization. Design work and UI /UX on mobile and desktop sites, and digital ads for: Frigidaire, Electrolux, State Farm, Reebok, USTA, RoC Skin Care, Aveeno, Lipton. Worked with developers to guide translation from design into digital product.

#### **Education**

#### SUMMER 2017

#### CODEUP

Completed 16-week software development immersive in San Antonio, consisting of 536+ hours of curriculum covering full-stack web development and associated technologies. Built various programming projects alone and in teams.

#### 2007-2010

#### **TEXAS STATE UNIVERSITY**

San Marcos, TX. BFA Communication Design. Summa Cum Laude.